Yeah, if you don't have the right
messages, um
you will not pick it up. That is for
sure.
>> You have to understand the right
message.
Is there a right message?
>> Well, the thing is
writing is like coding for computers.
You know,
um you have to read it and then
interpret it in your mind.
That's why they say all this is hidden.
Because it is. I mean, it's right there
in plain sight, but you have to decode
the information to make it work.
>> Sorry, guys. Had to restart it. I don't
know what happened there, but we should
be good now. There we go. Yep.
>> Yeah.
>> Got it.
>> Imagine that. Wi-Fi keeps dropping out.
Elon Musk does not want this information
on the internet.
If you think about it, the whole
universe is magnetism, though. Uh
the magnetic poles of planet Earth kind
of determine a lot on planet Earth.
Your heart pumps off of a positively
charged uh Na and a negative Well,
actually, yes. Positively charged Na